Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 (bulk 2007-2012)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 2007-2012
MS 545
Giffords, Gabrielle
This collection contains the political papers of Gabrielle Giffords that document her career as a member of the United States House of Representatives from 2007-2012 as well as the shooting at Giffords’ “Congress on your Corner” event on January 8, 2011. It is organized into 3 subgroups with the bulk of the collection found in the committee files as well as in materials related to the January 8th, 2011 Tucson, Arizona shooting. The collection also contains correspondence, legislative files, voting records, subject files, photographs and audio visual materials. This collection also contains a substantial amount of electronic records. THIS COLLECTION IS CURRENTLY CLOSED. PLEASE CONTACT AN ARCHIVIST IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO VIEW MATERIALS.
70 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/ E-Mail: LBRY-askspcoll@email.arizona.edu
Restrictions
THIS COLLECTION IS CURRENTLY CLOSED. PLEASE CONTACT AN ARCHIVIST IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO VIEW MATERIALS.
Biographical Note
Gabrielle Dee Giffords was born June 8, 1970 in Tucson, Arizona to Spencer and Gloria Giffords. She graduated from University High School in 1988 and attended Scripps College. Graduating in 1993, she majored in Latin American studies and sociology after which she won a Fulbright Scholarship and spent a year studying in Chihuahua, Mexico. She then attended Cornell University, graduating with a master’s degree in regional planning in 1996. She returned to Tucson to run her family tire business until it was sold in 2000. She married U.S. Navy pilot and NASA astronaut Mark Kelly in 2007.
In 2000 she ran for state office citing the difficulties in owning a small business as an impetus for running. She was elected to the Arizona House from 2001 to 2003 and the Arizona Senate from 2003 to 2005 when she resigned to pursue the soon to be vacated US House seat held by Congressman Jim Kolbe. She was elected to Arizona’s 8th congressional district for the 110th to 112th Congress. She served on the Armed Services, Foreign Affairs and Science and Technology committees throughout her congressional career. She was also the ranking member of the Space and Aeronautics subcommittee of the Space and Technology committee during the 111th Congress. She was a member of the Blue Dog Coalition, supported immigration reform and border security and was an advocate for solar energy.
On January 8, 2011 at a “Congress on your Corner” event a gunman killed six and injured 13 others. Federal Judge John Roll and Giffords staffer Gabriel Zimmerman were among those killed. Giffords was shot in the head but survived and made a remarkable recovery. She returned to the House to vote on the debt ceiling bill in August 2011 but resigned from Congress in January 2012 to focus on her recovery.
Since her resignation Giffords and her husband Mark Kelly have focused on gun control legislation. On the second anniversary of the Tucson shooting, they launched Americans for Responsible Solutions, a political action committee aimed at the prevention of gun violence and responsible gun ownership.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into 3 Subgroups
Subgroup I: Congressional Activities, 1995-2012
Series 1: Committee Files, 1995-2012
Subseries 1: Armed Services, 2005-2011
Subseries 2: Foreign Affairs, 2007-2010
Subseries 3: Science and Technology, 1995-2012
Series 2: Legislative Activity Files, 2007-2012
Series 3: Issue Files, 2005-2011
Series 4: Voting Records, 2008-2010
Series 5: Speeches, 2007-2011
Series 6: Correspondence, 2006-2012
Subseries 1: Acknowledgement and Invitations, 2007-2012
Subseries 2: Letters with other officials, 2006-2012
Subseries 3: Constituent mail, 2007-2012
Subseries 4: Form letters, 2009-2010
Series 7: Office Files, 2006-2011
Subseries 1: Schedules, 2009-2010
Subseries 2: Travel, 2007-2009
Subseries 3: Events, 2007-2011
Subseries 4: Staff Files, 2006-2011
Series 8: Press Files, 2007-2011
Subgroup II: Media Files, 2005-2012
Series 1: Photographs, 2006-2010
Series 2: Audio Visual Materials, 2005-2012
Subseries 1: Video cassettes, 2007, 2010
Subseries 2: Compact Discs, 2005-2012
Series 3: Memorabilia, 2006-2011
Subgroup III: January 8, 2011 Tucson, Arizona shooting, 2011-2012
Series 1: Correspondence, 2011
Series 2: Press Clippings, 2011-2012
Series 3: Audio visual material, 2011-2012
Series 4: Memorabilia, 2010-2012
Subgroup IV: Electronic records
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains the political papers of Democratic Congresswoman Gabrielle Giffords that document her career as a member of the United States House of Representatives in Arizona’s 8th District (2007-2012). The collection includes campaign materials, committee files, legislative files, voting records, speeches, office files, correspondence, press files and subject files as well as photographs and audio visual materials. Also included are materials related to the January 8, 2011 shooting of Gabrielle Giffords and 18 others at a Tucson “Congress on your Corner” event which includes correspondence such as well wishes, press clippings and memorabilia.
Contact Tucson’s January 8 Memorial Foundation for more information about materials related to the January 8th, 2011 shooting.
Access Terms
Giffords, Gabrielle D. (Gabrielle Dee), 1970-
Giffords, Gabrielle D. (Gabrielle Dee), 1970--Assassination attempt, 2011.
Legislators--United States--Archives.
Solar energy--Law and legislation--Arizona.
United States Politics and government--20th century.
Tucson (Ariz.) -- Politics and government.
Container List
- Subgroup I: Congressional Activities, 1995-2012
  This subgroup contains materials related to Giffords’ congressional career including committee files, legislative activity files, voting records, speeches, office files, correspondence, press files and issue files.
  - Series 1: Committee Files, 1995-2012
    This series contains materials related to Giffords’ committee work including her work on the Armed Services Committee, Subcommittee on Tactical Air and Land Forces and Subcommittee on Readiness; Foreign Affairs Committee, and the Science and Technology Committee, Subcommittee on Space and Aeronautics (ranking member) and Subcommittee on Technology and Innovation. It is arranged alphabetically.
    - Subseries 1: Armed Services, 2005-2011
      This subseries contains materials related to Giffords’ work on the Armed Services committee such as legislation, Dear Colleague letters, appropriations and issues related to the armed services.
      - 162nd Fighter Wing, Arizona Air National Guard, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Afghan Surge brief, January 21, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Air Force Energy mandates, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Air Guard, January 6, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Al Qa'ida in the Arabian Peninsula, January 20, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Amendment to National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2012, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - American Military Posture in United States European Command, Pacific Command and United States Forces Korea, March 24, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - American Military Posture in United States Northern Command and North American Aerospace Defense Command, United States South Command, United States Joint Forces Command and United States Africa Command, March 18, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Arizona Defense Consortium, April 28, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Army Training brief, February 11, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Asymmetric Threat Response and Analysis Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Biodefense and Pandemic Vaccine and Drug Development Act, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Border Violence Summit, April 7, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Briefing on United States-Iraq Status of Forces Agreement, November 18, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Chief Kermit Miller meeting memorandum, January 27, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - China Hearing, January 15, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Congressional delegation Giffords to Fort Bliss, Texas, August 24, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Congressional delegation Smith to Fort Huachuca, April 30, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base energy initiatives, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base solar power system environmental assessment, September, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Defense energy and environment issues, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Defense healthcare and disability benefits, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Defense priorities in the Obama Administration, January 27, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Department of Defense Energy Dear Colleagues (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Department of Defense Energy Dear Colleagues (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Department of Defense Energy letters, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (1 of 7), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (2 of 7), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (3 of 7), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (4 of 7), 2010 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (5 of 7), 2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (6 of 7), 2010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act (7 of 7), 2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act section by section summary (1 of 2), 2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Department of Defense Energy Security Act section by section summary (2 of 2), 2010 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Department of Defense Energy Task Force reports (1 of 2), May, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Department of Defense Energy Task Force reports (2 of 2), May, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Department of Defense at high risk, March 12, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Department of Defense renewable energy, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Energy and environment, space-based solar power, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Energy security, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Fighter Gap articles, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Figher Gap Task Force, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Final environmental assessment for a solar power system at the Davis-Monthan Air Force Base, September, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Fiscal Year 2009 National Defense Authorization Act, May 14, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Fiscal Year 2009 National Defense Authorization Act Conference report summary (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Fiscal Year 2011 President's budget request for national defense, February 3, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Fort Bliss energy brief, August 24, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Fort Bliss expansion program, August 24, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Fort Huachuca energy initiatives, September 10, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Fort Huachuca visit, July 12, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Fort Huachuca visit, March 21, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Gabrielle Giffords clips, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - General Armed Services, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - General energy (1 of 2), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - General energy (2 of 2), 2006-2010 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - GE, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - General House Armed Services Committee, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Global Financial Crisis, March 11, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Hearing on the Independent Review of the Shooting at Fort Hood, January 20, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - House Armed Services Committee 111th Organizational Paperwork, January 12, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 1246- Military Readiness Enhancement Act, Don't Ask Don't Tell, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 2647- National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2010 (1 of 3), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 2647- National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2010 (2 of 3), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 2647- National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2010 (3 of 3), 2009 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 5658- Appropriations Authorization, May 16, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Intel Reauthorization, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Intelligence and Security Command, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Joint Air Land and Seapower Subcommittee, Army and Marine Corps Reset, July 8, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Joint Air Land and Seapower Subcommittee, Operation Iraqi Freedom and Operation Enduring Freedom Force Protection Initiatives, February 4, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Joint Air Land and Seapower Subcommittee, Posture of United States Transportation Command, February 25, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Marine Corps Air Station, Yuma, Arizona, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Mark-up of the Guantanamo Resolution of Inquiry, December 14, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Mark-up of H.R. 5013- Improve Acquisition Act, April 21, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Medical MilCon, March 18, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Member Request Form, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Memorandum on Commander's Emergency Response Program Guidance, May 9, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Military Advisory Council, Re: Afghanistan, December 9, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Military Energy Initiatives, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Military Magazine Operations interview memorandum, January 5, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - North American Aerospace Defense Command/United States Northern Command, October 1, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Nellis Air Force Base Solar Reserve proposal, July 1, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Offset policy, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Operation Iraqi Freedom and Operation Enduring Freedom Intelligence, Surveillance, and Reconnaissance, March 4, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Overseas Environmental Impact statement (1 of 2), October, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Overseas Environmental Impact statement (2 of 2), October, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Piracy on the High Seas, March 5, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Preventing Weapons of Mass Destruction proliferation and terrorism, January 22, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Army Investigation of Arlington National Cemetery, June 30, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Department of Defense Land Acquisition and Strategy, February 24, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Department of Defense Operational Energy, March 3, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Effective Counterinsurgency Hearing, March 25, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Hearing on Installation Energy, February 24, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Military Construction, June 3, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Military Readiness proposal, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, National Security Personnel System Hearing, April 1, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Operations and Maintenance budget request, May 20, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Readiness Subcommittee, Readiness and Sustainment of the Navy Surface Fleet, March 25, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Reforming the Military Commissions Act, July 24, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Repair Network, 2008-2010 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Report on the Committee on Appropriations, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - Report on H.R. 5658- National Defense Authorization Act for Fiscal Year 2009, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - S. 3001 Appropriations Authorization for 2009, September 18, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Security Appropriations Earmarks, September, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Security and Stability in Afghanistan and Iraq, September 10, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Status of Forces Agreement brief, November 19, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Status of Operations in Afghanistan, June 16, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Air Sovereignty Alert Mission, April 22, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Army Modernization, May 21, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Battlefield Contracts, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Child Custody, June 16, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Civil Air Patrol, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Congressional Commission on the Strategic Posture, May 6, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Department of Defense at High Risk Hearing #2, May 6, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, F-22 Raptor Program, November 18, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Fort Huachuca visit, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Hearing on Afghanistan, Pakistan, United States Central Command and United States Special Operations Command, April 2, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Hearing on Effective Counterinsurgency in Pakistan, April 29, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, House Armed Services Committee Air and Land Subcommittee briefing on the status of Army Aviation, April 23, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, H.R. 2101- Weapons Acquisition System Reform Through Enhancing Technical Knowledge and Oversight Act, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, National Guard and Reserve Equipment Account, May 5, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Navy Posture (1 of 2), February 24, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Navy Posture (2 of 2), February 24, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Obsolete Significant Military Equipment, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Posture Hearing on the President's Fiscal Year 2010 Budget Request for Defense, May 13, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Quadrennial Defense Review, February 4, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Joint Improvised Explosive Device Defeat Organization, December 2, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, Status of Future Combat Systems, March 26, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, United States Air Force Modernization, May 20, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, United States Air Force Posture, May 19, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Tactical Air and Land Forces Subcommittee, United States Army Posture, May 14, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Tactical Aircraft Modernization, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - United States Army Installation Energy Program, September, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - United States Military Language and Culture, September 10, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - United States Policy in Afghanistan, October 14, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - United States Policy in Afghanistan, December 3, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - United States Strategy in Iraq and Afghanistan, February 12, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Veteran's Advisory Council, Improving Health and Medical Healthcare to Veterans and Military Personnel, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Weapons of Mass Destruction Threats, July 15, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Subseries 2: Foreign Affairs, 2007-2010
      This subseries contains materials related to Giffords’ work on the Foreign Affairs committee primarily legislation and issues related to the committee.
      - H.R. 1441- Stop Arming Iran Act, March 9, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - LGBT Issues (1 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - LGBT Issues (2 of 2), 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous International Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific, H.Res. 295, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific, H.R. 422- China Relations, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific, Korea Foreign Trade Agreement, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific, National Committee on United States-China Relations, April 28, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific, NTDTV and Eutelsat, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on Asia and the Pacific, Sri Lankan letters and articles, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on Europe, Eurasia, and Emerging Threats, Armenia H.Res. 106, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Subcommittee on Europe, Eurasia, and Emerging Threats, H.Con.Res. 151, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Subcommittee on the Middle East and North Africa, General Africa, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Subcommittee on the Middle East and North Africa, General Middle East, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Subcommittee on the Middle East and North Africa, Iran, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Subcommittee on the Middle East and North Africa, Iraq, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Subcommittee on the Middle East and North Africa, Israel, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Subcommittee on the Middle East and North Africa, Jewish Institute for National Security Affairs, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, Arizona Trade Data, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, Export Control, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, H.R. 3934- Affordable Footwear Act, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, Modifying of Free Trade Agreements, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, Panama Foreign Trade Agreement, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, Peru Foreign Trade Agreement, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Subcommittee on Terrorism, Nonproliferation, and Trade, Trade Adjustment Assistance Improvement Act, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Colombia Foreign Trade Agreement (1 of 2), 2008 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Colombia Foreign Trade Agreement (2 of 2), 2008 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Cuba, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Cuba, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, General Western Hemisphere, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Mexico-Merida International, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Mexico-United States Interparliamentary Group Meeting, June 8, 2007-June 10, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, Report Concerning the Merida Initiative, July 21, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, United States, Mexico, Canada Border Issues, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Subcommittee on the Western Hemisphere, United States-Mexico Relations, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)